A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Program and Policy, SG 3.5 FA1843
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Service Departments, 914; 22.41 Cubic Feet 59 letter document boxes
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Field Office records - Zimbabwe, 2000-2001 (Box 290, Folder 4)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Library, 1922; 1941-1977 (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Library, 1978-2004 (Box 291, Folder 2-4)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Library, 1978-2004 (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management, 1973-1999 (Box 292, Folder 1-3)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management, 2000-2009 (Box 292, Folder 4, Box 293, Folder 1-2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management, 2010-2014 (Box 284, Folder 4)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Filing Procedure Reports, 1931-1969 (Box 293, Folder 3)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Filing Procedure Reports, 1970s (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Filing Procedure Reports, 1980s (Box 294, Folder 2, Box 295, Folder 1-2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - GRM Information Management Services, 2004-2014 (Box 284, Folder 5)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Digitization of Hard Copy Records, 2004-2005 (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Naremco Consultancy, 2007-2009 (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Requests for Information, 1998-2000 (Box 296, Folder 1-2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Requests for Information, 2001-2002 (Box 297, Folder 1-3)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Requests for Information, 2003 (Box 297, Folder 4-5, Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Requests for Information, 2004-2006 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Requests for Information, 2007 (Box 298, Folder 3, Box 299, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Requests for Information, 2008-2009 (Box 299, Folder 2-4)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Requests for Information, 2010-2011 (Box 300, Folder 1-2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Requests for Information, 2011 (Box 300, Folder 3-4, Box 301, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Requests for Information, 2007-2012 (Box 301, Folder 2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Requests for Information, 2012-2013 (Box 301, Folder 3-4, Box 302, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Subject Classifying, 1964-1981 (Box 302, Folder 2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Management - Subject Classifying Appendices, 1966-1980 (Box 302, Folder 3-4, Box 303, Folder 1-2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Retention (RR), 1938-1987 (Box 303, Folder 3-4, Box 304, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Retention (RR), 1988 (Box 304, Folder 2-3)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Retention (RR), 1989-2006 (Box 304, Folder 4, Box 305, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Retention (RR) - Comptroller, 1964-2003 (Box 306, Folder 1)
    Permanently Restricted - Comptroller
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Retention (RR) - Financial Resources, 2004-2005 (Box 306, Folder 2)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Retention (RR) - Personnel, 1966-1980 (Box 306, Folder 3)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2051
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Records Retention (RR) - President's Office, 2007 (Box 306, Folder 4)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Rockefeller Archive Center - Front of File, 1974-2007 (Box 305, Folder 2-4)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Rockefeller Archive Center, 1980-2003 (Box 307, Folder 1-4)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Rockefeller Archive Center, 2004-2005 (Box 307, Folder 5)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Rockefeller Archive Center, 2006-2008 (Box 308, Folder 1-3)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Rockefeller Archive Center, 2008-2013 (Box 308, Folder 4, Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Records and Library Services (RLS) - Rockefeller Archive Center - Scholarly Resources, 1987-2003 (Box 309, Folder 2-3)
  - Research and Evaluation, 2007-2013 (Box 309, Folder 4, Box 310, Folder 1)
  - Research and Evaluation, 2007-2013 (Box 306, Folder 5)
  - Research and Records Department, 2011-2012 (Box 310, Folder 2)
  - Secretary's Office, 1997-2010 (Box 310, Folder 3)
  - Secretary's Office, 1997-2010 (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Secretary's Office - Program Guidebook, 2004-2005 (Box 312, Folder 1-2)
  - Secretary's Office, 1984 (Box 312, Folder 3-4)
  - Strategy and Evaluation Unit, 2011-2012 (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Strategy and Evaluation Unit, 2011-2012 (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1982; 1995 (Box 311, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's Office - Plan Investment Committee, 1995 (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Word Processing Study, 1977-1983 (Box 313, Folder 2)
  - Work Environment - Working Smarter Group, 1995-1996 (Box 313, Folder 3)
  - Special Leave Program, 1994 (Box 314, Folder 1)
  - Staff Relations, 1991-2013 (Box 314, Folder 2)
  - Staff Relations - Supplementary Material, 1991-2013 (Box 315, Folder 1-2)
  - Staff Relations - Awards Program, 1993 (Box 316, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2064
  - Staff Relations - Awards Program - Supplementary Material (Box 317, Folder 1)
  - Staff Relations - Conversation on Race, 1995-1998 (Box 317, Folder 2-3)
  - Staff Relations - Conversations on Race, 1999-2003 (Box 318, Folder 1-2)
  - Staff Relations - Conversations on Race - Supplementary Material, 1995-2003 (Box 319, Folder 1-2, Box 320, Box 321, Folder 1)
  - Staff Relations - Coordinator Administrative Research Associates Team (CARAT), 1998-2002 (Box 321, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's Office - Investment Strategy papers, 1994-1997 (Box 322, Folder 1-2)
- Counsel, 916; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Counsel, 1980-2004 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Permanently Restricted - Counsel
- Travel, 917; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Travel, 1991-2013 (Box 328, Folder 1-3)
- Agriculture, 923; 4.18 Cubic Feet 11 letter document boxes
  - Program and Policy, 1984-1990 (Box 322, Folder 3-5, Box 323, Folder 1)
  - Program and Policy, 1991-1994 (Box 323, Folder 2-4)
  - Program and Policy, 1995-1996 (Box 324, Folder 1-3)
  - Program and Policy, 1997-1998 (Box 324, Folder 4-5)
  - Program and Policy, 1999 (Box 325, Folder 1-2)
  - Program and Policy - Minutes, 1983-1999 (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - Program and Policy - Supplementary Material (Box 325, Folder 3-4, Box 326, Folder 1-4, Box 329, Folder 3, Box 330, Folder 1-2)
  - Program and Policy - Africa, 1982-1983 (Box 328, Folder 4-5, Box 329, Folder 1)
  - Program and Policy - Africa, 1984-1988 (Box 329, Folder 2)
  - Program and Policy - Africa, 1984-1988 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2059
  - Program and Policy - Conference, 1979-1981 (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - Program and Policy - Conference - Supplementary Material (Box 331, Folder 1-2)
- Arts and Humanities, 929; 3.8 Cubic Feet 10 letter document boxes
  - Program and Policy - Minutes, 1991-2004 (Box 331, Folder 3)
  - Program and Policy - Minutes, 1991-2004 (Box 333, Folder 1)
  - Program and Policy, 1982-1983 (Box 331, Folder 4-6)
  - Program and Policy, 1984-1985 (Box 332, Folder 1-3)
  - Program and Policy, 1986-1987 (Box 332, Folder 4, Box 334, Folder 1-2)
  - Program and Policy, 1988-1990 (Box 334, Folder 3-4, Box 335, Folder 1)
  - Program and Policy, 1991-1992 (Box 335, Folder 2)
  - Program and Policy, 1993 (Box 335, Folder 3)
  - Program and Policy, 1994-1995 (Box 336, Folder 1)
  - Program and Policy - Supplementary Material (Box 336, Folder 2-3)
  - Program and Policy - Reports on Arts and Humanities Program (PRO 1- Pro 1D), 1983 (Box 337, Folder 1-2)
  - Program and Policy - Amicus Curiae Briefs, 1997 (Box 337, Folder 3)
  - Program and Policy - "Freedom of Expression" Meeting, 1993 May (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - Program and Policy - Looking Ahead - Private Sector Giving to the Arts and Humanities, 1995 (Box 338, Folder 2)
  - Program and Policy - Media Worldwide, 1990-1992 (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - Program and Policy - Media Worldwide, 1990-1992 (Box 327, Folder 3)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2063
  - Program and Policy - Multiple-Year Support for Individual Artists (Failed Initiative), 1985-1987 (Box 339, Folder 1)
- Population Sciences, 930; 2.28 Cubic Feet 6 letter document boxes
  - Program and Policy - Population Growth and Environment in Less Developed Countries (LDCS) (Failed Initiative), 1990 (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - Program and Policy - Population Sciences, 1992-1993 (Box 339, Folder 3-5)
  - Program and Policy - Population Sciences, 1994-1998 (Box 340, Folder 1-4)
  - Program and Policy - Population Sciences, 1999-2002 (Box 341, Folder 1-3)
  - Program and Policy - Population Sciences, 1999-2002 (Box 333, Folder 2)
  - Program and Policy - Population Sciences, 1990-1991 (Box 341, Folder 4-5, Box 342, Folder 1)
  - Program and Policy - Population Sciences - 1999 Program Evaluation (Box 342, Folder 2-4, Box 343, Folder 1)
  - Program and Policy - Population Sciences - Trip Reports, 1991-1994 (Box 343, Folder 2-4)
- International, 100; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Claims (Unsubstantiated) - A-Z, 1970-1980 (Box 344, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Counsel
  - Claims (Unsubstantiated) - Aponte-Vazquez, 1981 (Box 344, Folder 2)
  - Claims (Unsubstantiated) - Craft v. Vanderbilt University, et. al., 1994 (Box 344, Folder 3)
  - Claims (Unsubstantiated) - Gilman v. Landesman and Rockefeller Foundation, 1977; 1982; 1985 (Box 344, Folder 4)
  - Claims (Unsubstantiated) - Clavey v. Madden, Halpert, RF, 1995 (Box 344, Folder 5)
  - Claims (Unsubstantiated) - Henley v. Vanderbilt University, et. al., 1994 (Box 344, Folder 6)
  - Claims (Unsubstantiated) - Office of Independent Counsel re: Costa Rica, 1987 (Box 344, Folder 7)
  - Claims (Unsubstantiated) - Hodaba v. Rockefeller Foundation, 1976-1979 (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - Claims (Unsubstantiated) - Warburg and the International Equity Trust Minnesota, 1987 (Box 345, Folder 2)
  - Claims (Unsubstantiated) - Wright v. 1000 Friends of Oregon, 1980 (Box 345, Folder 3)
  - Inventory - Donations (Equipment), 1924-2014 (Box 346, Folder 1-2)
  - Inventory - Tapes, 1988 (Box 346, Folder 3)
- Agricultural Institutes, 104; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Agricultural Institutes (CGIAR) - History, 1983-1986 (Box 346, Folder 4)
- International Relations, 155; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - International Economics in the Developing World (Proposed Program), 1985-1986 (Box 346, Folder 5)
- United States, 200; 2.93 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes and 3 legal document boxes
  - United States - General (No program letter)
    - Center for Employment Training - Job Training, 1982-1984 (Box 347, Folder 1-2)
    - Center for Employment Training - Job Training, 1985-1986 (Box 347, Folder 3, Box 348, Folder 1-2)
    - Center for Employment Training - Job Training - Supplementary Material, 1982-1983 (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - Center for Employment Training - Dissemination Project, 1990 (Box 348, Folder 4, Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Center for Employment Training - Dissemination Project, 1991 (Box 349, Folder 2-4)
    - Center for Employment Training - Dissemination Project, 1992 (Box 350, Folder 1-3)
    - Center for Employment Training - Dissemination Project, 1993-1995 (Box 350, Folder 4, Box 351, Folder 1-4)
    - Center for Employment Training - Dissemination Project - Supplementary Material (Box 351, Folder 5, Box 352, Folder 1-3)
    - Foundations, Criticism of, 1971-1986 (Box 352, Folder 4)
    - Price Waterhouse and Company Grant Accounting (No Grant), 1986 (Box 352, Folder 5)
  - United States - Medical Sciences, 200A
    - Cornell University - Contraceptive Steroids, 1978 (Box 353, Folder 1)
    - Cornell University - Human Follicle - Stimulating Hormone Research, 1979 (Box 353, Folder 2)
  - United States - Social Sciences, 200S
    - New York University - Income Maintenance Policy - Supplementary Material, 1970 (Box 353, Folder 3)
- Fellowships for American Playwrights, 272; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Minutes, 1989 (Box 354, Folder 1)
- India, 464; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Administration, 1988 (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - Contraceptive Methods Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 354, Folder 3)
- Kenya, 476; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Administration, 1986-1998 (Box 354, Folder 4)
- East Africa, 477; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - Administration, 1984-1991 (Box 355, Folder 1-3)
- Malawi/Nyasaland, 482; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Administration, c. 2000 (Box 356, Folder 1)
- Thailand, 617; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - Administration, 1991 (Box 355, Folder 5)
  - Donation of Equipment, 1983 (Box 355, Folder 6)
- Indonesia, 652; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - Administration, 1983 (Box 355, Folder 7)
- South Africa, 789; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - Administration, 1992 (Box 355, Folder 4)
- Sweden, 800; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Nobel Prize, 1969-2013 (Box 357, Folder 1-3)
- Israel, 825; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Weizmann Institute - Hormonal Steroids Congress, 1982-1984 (Box 357, Folder 4)